halftermdates.co.uk 2018-12-18

# Privacy Policy - Ofsted School Inspection Ratings - KS2 KS4 Results

## Who we are

Our website address is: http://www.halftermdates.co.uk.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymised string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

## Who we share your data with

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognise and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## Google Cookie Policy

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to this website and/or other websites.  
Google’s use of advertising cookies enables it and its advertising partners to serve adverts based on your visit to this website and/or other sites on the Internet.

> You may opt out of personalised advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated)

In addition, we use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google’s privacy policy is available at: <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>

Whilst every effort is made to ensure that the traffic reports displayed on this website are accurate, there are occasions when circumstances beyond our control may result in changes to published content.

By using our website you agree to allow a local cookie to store some of your information, which is used to serve relevant adverts to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies then please, [click here before continuing](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/ "Google Adverts Policy") to use this website.

## Contact the Webmaster

Half Term Dates is an independent website displaying education information obtained from Open Source Data. To contact the webmaster with regards to technical issues, please email:

 **email:** info@halftermdates.co.uk

Contact Webmaster: [Malcolm Oakley](https://plus.google.com/+MalcolmOakley "Malcolm Oakley - Google+") on Google+

Based in Devon UK.
